(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.2",
"generated_at": "2026-06-22T10:36:14.141836",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
聖なる夜
Holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
a miracle begins.
さあ！
Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap across!
ハイになって灰になるまで 楽しんできな
Have fun until you get high and turn to ash!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even to the other side of the ocean!
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
Wow...
Gimme gimme gimme 愛
Gimme, gimme, gimme love!
Wow...
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close you could almost touch them.
聖なる夜
Holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
a miracle begins.
さあ！
Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap across!
ハイになって灰になるまで 楽しんできな
Have fun until you get high and turn to ash!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even to the other side of the ocean!
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
Wow...
Gimme gimme gimme 愛
Gimme, gimme, gimme love!
Wow...
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close you could almost touch them.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...a miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we go from high to ash
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', beyond the sea
もっと もっと近づきたいの
More and more, I want to get closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
...a live event where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと高く飛びたいの
More and more, I want to fly higher
Hyper jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close you could almost touch.
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live stream to watch, to a live event to meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...a miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we go from high to ash
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', beyond the sea
もっと もっと近づきたいの
More and more, I want to get closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
...a live event where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと高く飛びたいの
More and more, I want to fly higher
Hyper jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close you could almost touch.
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live stream to watch, to a live event to meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
聖なる夜
４つの星が、ひとつになるとき
Holy night
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Getting high until we burn to ashes
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to the other side of the sea
もっと
More
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
Woh...
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want my heart to race, gimme gimme gimme love
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
Woh...
もっと
More
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly even higher
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
I'm here. Close enough to touch.
ねぽらぼライブ re:Vision Holoearth Live
Nebolabo Live re:Vision Holoearth Live
Hyper Jumpin' now!
2025.12.21 Sun
Sunday, December 21, 2025
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert you watch, to a concert where you can meet.
聖なる夜
４つの星が、ひとつになるとき
Holy night
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Getting high until we burn to ashes
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to the other side of the sea
もっと
More
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
Woh...
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want my heart to race, gimme gimme gimme love
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
Woh...
もっと
More
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly even higher
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
I'm here. Close enough to touch.
ねぽらぼライブ re:Vision Holoearth Live
Nebolabo Live re:Vision Holoearth Live
Hyper Jumpin' now!
2025.12.21 Sun
Sunday, December 21, 2025
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert you watch, to a concert where you can meet.
聖なる夜
４つの星が、ひとつになるとき
Holy night
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Getting high until we burn to ashes
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to the other side of the sea
もっと
More
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
Woh...
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want my heart to race, gimme gimme gimme love
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
Woh...
もっと
More
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly even higher
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
I'm here. Close enough to touch.
ねぽらぼライブ re:Vision Holoearth Live
Nebolabo Live re:Vision Holoearth Live
Hyper Jumpin' now!
2025.12.21 Sun
Sunday, December 21, 2025
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert you watch, to a concert where you can meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When the four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さぁ
Now!
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to ash!
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', to the other side of the sea!
みるだけじゃない
It's not just for watching!
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together!
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere!
もっともっと
More, more!
高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher!
Hyper jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Here I am. So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper jumpin' now
聖なる夜
Holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When the four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さぁ
Now!
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to ash!
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', to the other side of the sea!
みるだけじゃない
It's not just for watching!
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together!
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere!
もっともっと
More, more!
高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher!
Hyper jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Here I am. So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper jumpin' now
聖なる夜
Holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When the four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さぁ
Come on!
hyper jumpin’ 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to ash,
ダンシング
Dancing...
hyper jumpin’ 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', to the other side of the sea,
もっと もっと近づきたいの
More, more, I want to get closer.
みるだけじゃない
Not just for watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together!
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
More, more, I want to fly higher.
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. Close enough to touch.
2025.12.21 Sun
出演：桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Sunday, December 21, 2025
Cast: Momosuzu Nene, Omaru Polka, Yukihana Lamy, Shishiro Botan
会場：HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert to watch, to a concert to meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to Join Neporabo Live
ホロアースからの参加
Joining from Holoearth
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
Neporabo Support Set
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Neporabo Live Memorial T-Shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
Neporabo Live Photo Contest
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さぁ
Come on!
hyper jumpin’ 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to ash,
ダンシング
Dancing...
hyper jumpin’ 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', to the other side of the sea,
もっと もっと近づきたいの
More, more, I want to get closer.
みるだけじゃない
Not just for watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together!
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
More, more, I want to fly higher.
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. Close enough to touch.
2025.12.21 Sun
出演：桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Sunday, December 21, 2025
Cast: Momosuzu Nene, Omaru Polka, Yukihana Lamy, Shishiro Botan
会場：HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert to watch, to a concert to meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to Join Neporabo Live
ホロアースからの参加
Joining from Holoearth
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
Neporabo Support Set
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Neporabo Live Memorial T-Shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
Neporabo Live Photo Contest
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さぁ
Come on!
hyper jumpin’ 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to ash,
ダンシング
Dancing...
hyper jumpin’ 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', to the other side of the sea,
もっと もっと近づきたいの
More, more, I want to get closer.
みるだけじゃない
Not just for watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together!
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
More, more, I want to fly higher.
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. Close enough to touch.
2025.12.21 Sun
出演：桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Sunday, December 21, 2025
Cast: Momosuzu Nene, Omaru Polka, Yukihana Lamy, Shishiro Botan
会場：HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert to watch, to a concert to meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin' let's jump over it!
ハイになって 灰になるまで 楽しむ気だ！
Getting high, I'm in the mood to enjoy myself until I turn to ash!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin' to the other side of the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
More and more, I want to get closer!
Woah-oh, woah, woah-oh-oh-oh
ドキドキしたい gimme, gimme, gimme 愛
I want my heart to race, gimme, gimme, gimme love!
Woah-oh, woah, woah-oh-oh-oh
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
More and more, I want to fly higher!
Hyper jumpin' now!
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close you can almost touch us.
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch, to a live show you meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin' let's jump over it!
ハイになって 灰になるまで 楽しむ気だ！
Getting high, I'm in the mood to enjoy myself until I turn to ash!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin' to the other side of the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
More and more, I want to get closer!
Woah-oh, woah, woah-oh-oh-oh
ドキドキしたい gimme, gimme, gimme 愛
I want my heart to race, gimme, gimme, gimme love!
Woah-oh, woah, woah-oh-oh-oh
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
More and more, I want to fly higher!
みなさん、メリークリスマス！
Everyone, Merry Christmas!
本日はねぽらぼライブ re:VISIONにご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much for coming to Nepolabo Live re:VISION today!
ライブ開始はこの後19時からの予定となっていますので、今しばらくお待ちください。
The live concert is scheduled to start after this at 19:00, so please wait a little longer.
本公演のチラ見せ部分は、動画のYouTubeへの投稿が可能です！
You can post video clips of the sneak peek portion of this concert on YouTube!
かー！しかし！
Whoa! However!
他のSNSは、音声なしの30秒以内の動画の投稿をお願いします！
For other social media platforms, please limit posts to videos of 30 seconds or less with no audio!
静止画のスクリーンショットや、感想などは全編を通じて可能なので、いっぱい呟きお願いします！
Still screenshots and your impressions can be posted from the entire show, so please tweet a lot!
はーい！
Okay!
禁止事項ですが、本公演のミラー配信、並びに音声ありのライブ本編動画の一部SNSへの投稿となっています。
As for prohibited actions, mirror streaming of this show and posting clips of the main show with audio to social media are prohibited.
音声なしでも、30秒を超える動画のSNS投稿も禁止となっています。
Even without audio, posting videos exceeding 30 seconds on social media is also prohibited.
ルールを正しく守って、ライブを楽しんでくださいね！
Please follow the rules correctly and enjoy the live concert!
せーの！
One, two!
さあ、みんな！遊びに来る準備はできてるかな？
Now, everyone! Are you ready to come play?
ねねが描いた服、着てる人いるかな？
Is anyone wearing the clothes Nene drew?
雪民さんたちがどんな姿で会いに来てくれるか楽しみ！
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of form the Yukimin will come to see us in!
ホロアースのライブだから、好きな服装でライブ見れるのもいいよね。
Since it's a Holoearth live, it's great that we can watch it in whatever clothes we like, right?
スクショも撮っていいみたいなので、色んな角度から、たっくさん撮ってほしいです！
Since we can also take screenshots, I want you to take lots from various angles!
そう、普通のライブだと、動いて見て回ったりはできないもんね。
Right! In a normal live, you can't walk around and look, can you?
ねねたちの最高な写真、期待してるぞー！
We're expecting your best photos of us!
というわけで、ライブ開始までもうしばらくお待ちください。
Therefore, please wait a little longer until the live starts.
一緒にライブ盛り上がっていこう！
Let's get fired up for the live together!
おー！
Yeah!
Hyper jumpin' now
ねぽらぼライブRe:Vision始まるぞー！
Nepolabo Live Re:Vision is starting!
Hyper jumpin' now
ちょっと早めのクリスマス！盛り上がっていくぞ！
A slightly early Christmas! Let's get fired up!
Hyper jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper jumpin' let's jump out
come on baby 輝いて
come on baby shine
ハート きゅんって pump it up
My heart goes kyun and pump it up
Hyper jumpin’ 夢の先まで
Hyper jumpin' beyond the dream
もっと もっと 刺激が欲しいの
More, more, I want more excitement
はい！みんなでジャンプ！せーの！
Yes! Everyone jump! One, two...
はい！はい！はい！はい！
High! High! High! High!
Hyper jumpin' now
はい！はい！はい！はい！
High! High! High! High!
Hyper jumpin'
子どもくらい はしゃぐ方がお徳でしょ
Isn't it better to have fun like a kid?
ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
低気圧から 這い上がっていくテンション
Tension rising from the low pressure
ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
酔いながら 打ち返し まくる @(メンション)
While drunk, I keep fighting back with mentions
ラミィ！ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
カートを 乗りこなして 進むミッション
Mission to advance, riding the cart
ぼたん！ぼたん！ぼたん！
Botan! Botan! Botan!
このまま スピード 加速して
Speed up like this
たどり着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what's waiting at the end
止まらない 気持ちは 助走つけて
Unstoppable feelings, with a running start
次元を 超えていこう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さぁ
Come on
Hyper jumpin’ 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper jumpin' let's fly
ハイ になって 灰になるまで
Until I'm high and turn to ash
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing shake it up
Hyper jumpin’ 空の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin' beyond the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
More, more, I want to get closer
(woh…)
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want to get excited, gimme gimme gimme love
(woh…)
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
More, more, I want to fly higher
はい！はい！360度、楽しめてるか？
Yes! Yes! Are you enjoying it 360 degrees?
Hyper jumpin' now
右！左！ジャンプ！せーの！
Right! Left! Jump! One, two...
はい！はい！はい！はい！
High! High! High! High!
Hyper jumpin'
斜めから 攻めて 解決q(クエスション)
Solving the question by attacking from an angle
ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
ネガティブを 切り裂いてくれる チェンソー
A chainsaw that cuts through the negative
ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
流れる コメントと 掛け合いセッション
A session interacting with the flowing comments
ラミィ！ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
エイムを 鍛えて 狙い撃つ flick shot
Flick shot, aiming and shooting with trained aim
手を上にあげてー！
Put your hands up!
disは no no
dis is no no
好きなら more more more
If you like it, more more more
邪魔する ノイズは
Shooting down the interfering noise
撃ち消せ bang bang bang
bang bang bang
遊びたいだけ
I just want to play
アンチは 無視して
Ignore the antis
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off
蹴飛ばせ kick it！！
Kick them away, kick it!!
jump around！！
jump around!!
このまま 僕らは 旅をして
We'll continue our journey like this
たどり着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what's waiting at the end
信じた 未来と リンクして
Linking with the future we believed in
次元を 超えていこう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さぁ
Come on
Hyper jumpin’ 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin' let's jump over
ハイになって灰になるまで ダンシング shake it up
Until we go high and turn to ash, dancing shake it up!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで もっと
Hyper Jumpin' to the other side of the sea, more...
もっと近づきたいの
...more, I want to get closer.
(Woh...) ドキドキしたい
(Woh...) I want my heart to race...
Gimme gimme gimme 愛
...Gimme gimme gimme love.
(Woh...) もっと
(Woh...) More...
もっと高く飛びたいの
...more, I want to fly higher.
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ Hyper Jumpin' now
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hyper Jumpin' now!
ハイパー・ジャンピン！
Hyper Jumpin'!
いぇーい！やったー！
Yay! We did it!
「みんな元気ー？」「元気だよー！」
"Is everyone doing great?" "We're great!"
「というわけで、自己紹介いきましょう！」「ねねちから！」
"Alright, let's do our self-introductions!" "Starting with Nenechi!"
じゃあ、みんなアイテムとかの準備いいですか？
Now, is everyone ready with your items and things?
順番に行きますからね。みんなアイテムの準備してください。
We'll go in order, so everyone, please get your items ready.
「ね・ぽ・ら・ぼ」で行くからね！
We're going in order of "Ne-Po-Ra-Bo", okay?
どれくらい待つ？この準備。
How long should we wait for this preparation?
ちょっと待った方がいいか。
Maybe we should wait just a bit.
みんなアイテムをショートカットとかに入れといてね。
Make sure to put your items in your shortcut keys.
1、2、3、4って連打してね。取り出してね。
Spam 1, 2, 3, 4! Take them out.
よっしゃー！4、3、2、1、はいどうぞ！ねねさん！
Alright! 4, 3, 2, 1, and go! Nene-san!
はーい！
Okay!
じゃあみんな行くよ！飛んでね！ねぽらぼの「ね」、みんなの心の、せーの…
Alright everyone, here I go! Jump! The "Ne" of Nepolabo, everyone's heart... Ready, set...
エナジードリンク！
Energy drink!
はっしゅ、桃鈴ねねです！よろしくね！
Hasshu! I'm Momosuzu Nene! Nice to meet you!
「じゃあ次！」「はい、切り替えて、切り替えて！」
"Okay, next!" "Yes, switch over, switch over!"
ぽまるポルカだよ！
I'm Pomaru Polka!
いつものないか。ポルカおるか？
Wait, there's no "usual"? Polka, are you here?
おるよー！
Yes, I'm here!
ねぽらぼの「ぽ」、尾丸ポルカです！よろしく！
The "Po" of Nepolabo, I'm Omaru Polka! Nice to meet you!
いぇーい！
Yay!
こんらみ！
Kon-Lamy!
ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです。
I'm Yukihana Lamy from Hololive 5th Gen.
ラミィちゃんしか？
Only Lamy-chan?
おらーーん！
No one else!
はい、そして！
And finally!
はい、最後、最後！みんな！
Yes, last but not least! Everyone!
準備してる？準備してる？
Is everyone ready? Are you ready?
何の準備？
Ready for what?
スタンプ、スタンプ、スタンプあるじゃん！
Stamps, stamps! You have stamps, right?
ララライオン！
Lalala-lion!
ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたんです！
Hololive 5th Gen, I'm Shishiro Botan!
いぇーい！お祝いいただきます！いただきますよ！
Yay! Let's receive the celebrations! We'll take them!
皆さんね、ばっちり決まったところで、新しい試み「Re:Vision」ライブということで！
Now that everyone is fully introduced, this is our new project, "Re:Vision" Live!
詳しいことは概要欄やホロアースの公式ホームページを確認してください！
For more details, please check the description box or the official Holoearth website!
はい、ということでね、今日はでも、みんながね、アバターで参加してるし、いろんな角度からのこの振り付け？確認してほしいなと思います。
Yes, so today, since everyone is participating with their avatars, we want you to check out our choreography from various angles!
ねねの服着てる人はいると信じてるからね、みんな！
I believe there are people wearing Nene's outfit out there, okay everyone?
みんなもっとよく動いてみて！いいよいいよー！
Everyone, try moving around more! Looking good, looking good!
あ、いいよ！いいよ！
Ah, nice! Nice!
こっちが写真撮るんだね。
We are the ones taking pictures.
みんなとやれることなんかない？おまる。
Isn't there something we can do with everyone, Omaru?
え、何かな？何でしょうかね。
Eh, what could it be? I wonder what.
よし、あれやろう、あれ！
Alright, let's do THAT!
みんなで走りましょう、皆さん！
Let's run together, everyone!
走るよ！ここから！
We're running! Starting from here!
ポルカが先頭で、大外回って走ってみよう！
Polka will lead, and let's run along the outermost track!
おっけー、じゃあみんな集合、集合！
Okay, everyone, gather up, gather up!
みんなついてきてね！
Everyone, follow us!
じゃあ「せーの」で行くか？
Then shall we go on "ready, set"?
はい！
Yes!
じゃあ、せーの！うわーー！
Then, ready, set, go! Whoaaa!
全然ついてこないやつがいます！
There are some who aren't following at all!
あれ？あれ？
Huh? Huh?
はいはいはいはいはいはい！早くしてください！
Yes, yes, yes, yes! Hurry up, please!
ラミィさん、ついてこれないよ！大丈夫？
Lamy-san, you can't keep up! Are you okay?
反対回り行くよ！せーの！うわーー！
We're going the opposite way now! Ready, set, go! Whoaaa!
全然本気じゃない奴がいます！
There's someone who isn't trying seriously at all!
大丈夫？はい、本気の見せて、本気の見せて！
Are you okay? Show us your serious face, show us!
あれ？一周遅れてる？逆に。
Wait, is she a lap behind? On the contrary.
はい、お疲れ様！みんなお疲れ様！
Okay, good job! Good job, everyone!
みんなと走れて楽しい！
Running with everyone is so fun!
一緒に走れることなかなか無いからね。
We rarely get to run together like this.
あ、ちなみにですね、本番の曲の最中ですが、周りの人がジャンプする時とかも見えやすいように配慮してください！
Ah, by the way, during the actual performance, please be considerate so that others can easily see when people are jumping!
ジャンプ！ピョンピョンピョン！
Jump! Pyon, pyon, pyon!
周りの人に配慮して！配慮して！
Be considerate of those around you! Be considerate!
はい、盛り上がってるところ申し訳ないんですが、ここで悲しいお知らせがあります。
Yes, I'm sorry to interrupt while we're having so much fun, but we have some sad news here.
えー！何ー？
Eh! What is it?
ということで皆さん、すみません。YouTubeとホロアースのエントランスであるポータルスクエアでの無料配信はここまでとなっております。
So everyone, we are very sorry. The free broadcast on YouTube and the Entrance Portal Square of Holoearth ends here.
イェーイ！
Yeah!
はい。すいません。
Okay, excuse me.
引き続き、ホロアース、スマホ、そして最後では...
Next, on Holoearth, smartphones, and finally...
...ライブが配信されますので...
...the live concert will be streamed...
YouTubeで見てる方は動画の概要欄をチェックしてください！
So, if you're watching on YouTube, please check the video description!
はい！
Okay!
はい、で、チケット持っている、まだこっちに来てないポータルスクエアのみんなは...
Okay, and for everyone in Portal Square who has a ticket but hasn't come over here yet...
よかったらこっちに来てください。
...please come over here if you'd like!
えー、じゃあ、というわけで...
Well then, anyway...
YouTubeのみんな、バイバーイ！
Everyone on YouTube, bye-bye!
バイバーイ！
（さわやかだな。）
Bye-bye!
(That was refreshing.)
というわけで、次からはソロ曲ですが...
Anyway, next up are the solo songs...
まずは、誰からかな？
First, who will it be?
誰かな？誰かな？
Who is it? Who is it?
誰かな？誰かな？お前？お前？
Who is it? Who is it? You? You?
誰かな？
Who is it?
ねねちゃん！
Nene-chan!
それではよろしく！
Take it away!
みんな、どんどん盛り上がっていくぞー！
Everyone, let's keep getting hyped up!
おー！
Yeah!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.